Clayton H. Zaugg

2319 W. 4805 S. Taylorsville, UT 84129 <u>czaugg@student.neumont.edu</u> (702) 689-2007

Creative Web Developer and Successful Project Manager

Summary

- Creative UX / UI Developer with experience in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Accomplished leader with 10 plus years of delivering effective and profitable results
- Experience designing and implementing Project Management strategies

Core Competencies	Development Tools	Technical Skills
HTML	Git & Perforce SVN	UI / UX
CSS	Sublime Text / Brackets	OOP (Object-Oriented
JavaScript / JQuery	Adobe Creative Suite	Programming)
Node.JS	Visual Studio 2012	Wireframing
MongoDB	SQL Server 2012	Project Management
 Adobe Creative Suite 	Eclipse	SCRUM & Agile
jQuery UI Widgets	Windows, Linux, and OS X	Methodologies

Project Experience Project	Roles & Responsibilities	Date
MaritzCX - UI/UX Dev. Team Development of core product at MaritzCX	 Frontend Developer Redesigned and retooled the company's UI Library from a long scrolling site, to a single page app. Implemented solutions from multiple user stories using JavaScript, Marionette.JS, and JQuery Resolved bugs through the use of development tools like JIRA and Perforce SCRUM and Agile Methodologies followed daily so as to be consistent with company procedures Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Backbone.JS, Marionette.JS, .NET, Perforce SVN 	Jan 2015
BisiApp – Capstone Project Automated Inventory Control System for SoHo users to easily control and manage their inventory	 Project Developer Developed with Node.JS using Express, Passport, Mongoose, EJS, and other NPM modules Left comfort zone and installed Linux Mint, forcing myself to develop in a Linux environment Conceived the idea, drafted a project proposal, defended it for approval, spent ten weeks designing, developing, testing, and at the end, 20 minutes presenting it before a panel of professors for a pass / fail grade Technologies: Node.JS, MongoDB, EJS, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Photoshop, Linux, Bootstrap, git 	Sep 2014
Cook It - Project Showcase Winner Windows application for recipe discovery based on ingredients on hand, or almost on hand	 Team Leader UX / UI lead on a team of three, making final decisions on UX / UI concept implementation Used Entity framework within .NET Implemented JavaScript with MVC framework Technologies: MVC .NET 4.0, SQL Server, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Photoshop, SCRUM, git 	Oct 2013

Work History

 Codale Electric Supply 	Project Manager	11/2004 - 05/2012
 CompUSA 	Assistant Sales Manager	02/2003 - 11/2004
Microsoft	Team Lead	06/2001 - 02/2003

Education

Bachelor of Science Web Design & Development

Expected 06/2015

Neumont University

Honors/ Awards

Project Showcase Winner	10/2013
Microsoft Quarterly Customer Satisfaction Award	08/2002

Activities

- Neumont University Student Body President
- Neumont University Business Leaders
- Climbers of Neumont President